Three things you would like to do in the future
Now, Aira's three things she would like to do in the future.
What is the second thing you would like to do?
Yes, here is the second one!
Ding!
Studying abroad for a month!
Yo!
The very first time I went abroad was to Australia.
I was allowed to go on a school excursion.
Before that, I was afraid to get on a plane, and I never wanted to go abroad.
But after I went to Australia, my thinking changed 180 degrees.
Of course I wanted to learn English, and I also wanted to study abroad, but the most important thing was that I wanted to live abroad, because the ocean is beautiful, and the time passes very slowly in the cities where you can buy food together, and you can feel very gentle and kind.
I was thinking of going to college when I graduated from high school, and I was planning to go to a college where I could study abroad.
I've been thinking about going to college when I graduate from high school, and I'm also planning to go to a university where I can study abroad.
I would like to go to Austalia one more time, and I would like to go to France when I go there, and I would like to live the life of a foreign girl.
I want to live the life of a foreign girl.
Running along the river in the morning.
Then I pick out some fashions and put on my makeup.
Then I go to school.
Then you go to school and have a party with your friends.
You go to a party with them.
At night, you go to a home party with everyone at home, right?
I want to live like that.
That's the kind of life I want.
I have a longing for it.
I have a longing.
I love a foreign musical movie called High School Musical.
High School Musical.
I've had a yearning for it for a long time.
I want to live like that.
How much English do you speak, Aira?
I don't speak any English.
Is that so?
Yes. I studied English for a while.
I was studying a language for a while, but I was told by people around me that it doesn't matter if you study grammar by yourself.
They say that practice is the best way to get better, so I thought it might be worthwhile to study by myself.
On the other hand, I'm trying to watch foreign movies in English, but my English is weak.
Pronunciation seems to be the most important thing.
But I'm practicing my pronunciation with American Flash songs.
That's true.
There's a lot of English in the songs of AmeFlash.
The first song that had a lot of English in it
Bad Girl.
I really struggled with it at the beginning.
I couldn't even say the word "Girl".
I didn't know that the "R" had to roll off the tongue.
I didn't know that.
How did you practice?
I just listened to native speakers.
I took voice memos from people like Girger.
I would spend 3 to 40 minutes on each word, practicing with a slightly different pronunciation,
Even if you are practicing by yourself, you don't know if you are doing it or not,
I realized how important it is to really practice with your own voice.
What would you like to do in the future?
What do you want to do in this program?
Yuki-chan,
Kei-san,
I would like to thank everyone who participated in this program,
Makonen-san, and Pyo-chan.
Thank you very much!